<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Items>
    <HelpItem>
      <Entity>villageSign1</Entity>
<Text>Important message for Koowaalaas from other villages: Carbwir is a mess, so watch your step. Look around you to see where you can go and to inspect your surroundings.
If you have forgotten how to move, just {point the mouse|use your right thumbstick} to look around and {press the WSAD or arrow keys|use your right thumbstick} to move. If you need to jump, press the {space bar|A button}. 
Good luck, visitor!</Text>
    </HelpItem>
    <HelpItem>
      <Entity>villageSign2</Entity>
<Text>Problem Plaza. This statue was built for the villagers of Carbwir to honor the brave Koowaalaas who, years ago, brought great prosperity to this village. 
For each of the eight Development Goals of the United Nations he achieved, a symbol has been forged out of the purest gold. The more a goal is represented, the more the symbol will shine. If a goal is poorly represented, the symbol will decay.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
    <HelpItem>
      <Entity>villageSign3</Entity>
      <Text>Warning: these stables are unsafe!
This used to be the primary source of food for the village. Unless you are foolish enough to try and repair the stables, please go away.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
    <HelpItem>
      <Entity>villageSign4</Entity>
      <Text>Please, drink your own water! This well is empty.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
    <HelpItem>
      <Entity>villageSign5</Entity>
      <Text>To all people: This gate has been locked.
The key is lost. We're waiting for the WVHO to replace the gates.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign01</Entity>
      <Text>Hello Tubbles!
You've just entered the Dreamworld.
Go straight ahead to start a tutorial. If you wish to skip this, press {escape|the start button}.
-Morwir</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign03</Entity>
      <Text>We just actived your Axle Gizmo, this will allow you to rotate platforms across a certain axis.
First, you can select a group of platforms, indicated by their color, by pointing your crosshair at them. When selected, they will light up. The center of the group, around which the platforms are rotated, are indicated by the glowy thingies.
Then, you can rotate them, using your Axle Gizmo, down in your screen. Select an axis or rotation by using {the scrollwheel|the shoulderbuttons}. The Gizmo's axis you've selected will rotate in the given direction.
Once you've selected the axis and/or rotation, use {left-click|press B} to apply your rotation.
In front of you are two platforms, blue and green, go ahead and test it out!</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign06</Entity>
      <Text>Now that you've practiced rotating platforms, let's put it to use!
In front of you is a red group of platforms. Stand on the platform in front of you, select the group and rotate it along the horizontal axis twice to get across.
One more thing: If need an overview of the level, you can see it by holding {tab|the back button}.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign07</Entity>
      <Text>Well done! Now you need to jump.
You've already learned how (remember, by pressing the {space bar|A button}). Do this now by jumping across the gaps.
P.S. There's cake at the end.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign08</Entity>
      <Text>Sorry, the cake was a lie.
In front of you is a green platform which you can't reach. Rotate it towards you, stand on it, and rotate it back to get across.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign09</Entity>
      <Text>For the next puzzle, you'll need to use a different axis. See if you can figure it out.
Hint: Think about your position when rotating the orange platform.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign10</Entity>
      <Text>The blue platform is stuck! 
See if you can use the various axis to position it so you can jump across.
Hint: Think vertically.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign11</Entity>
      <Text>Great, you did it!
With the basics learnt, you are now ready to face the real puzzles representing the eight Development Goals.
And just in time, the potion is beginning to wear out. Good luck!</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>puzzleSign01</Entity>
      <Text>Welcome back to the Dreamworld, Tubbles.
You have chosen to enter through the Stable and the problem for this puzzle is hunger. The stable has collapsed and the villagers have no other viable source of food. 
If you solve the puzzle, its real world effect will a be a rebuilt stable and therefore a steady foodsupply for the village.
On the meadow to your left is another sign that will help you solve the puzzle.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>puzzleSign02</Entity>
      <Text>This puzzle is about food! 
As you can see, there are two pairs of cows in this puzzle. Unlike platforms, they're not connected to a center (the glowing thingies), instead, they rotate around each other. Select one cow and it'll rotate around the other. And vice versa.
As such, the cows are linked together. When you move one cow onto a platform, but the other cow is not on the same platform, the cows will fall when you move the platform.
Your goal is to get both pairs to the other meadow, across the puzzle. Good luck!
P.S. If a cow falls down, the both of the pair will be respawned in this meadow.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
    <HelpItem>
      <Entity>villageSignAfterTutorial</Entity>
      <Text>Now that you've learned how the Dreamworld works, find a spot that could use some improvement.
At this moment there is only one, more will be available in later versions of the game.
Hint: Look for some collapsed stables near the crates.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
    <HelpItem>
      <Entity>villageSignAfterPuzzle1</Entity>
      <Text>Congratulations! You've finished this version of Dreamworld.
As you can see, life is a little brighter in the village. The cows are back!</Text>
    </HelpItem>
  </Items>
</Help>