<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Items>
    <HelpItem>
      <Entity>villageSign1</Entity>
<Text>Important message for Koowaalaa's from other villages: Carbwir is a mess, so watch your steps. Look around you to see where you can go and to inspect your surroundings. If you have forgotten how to move your head or body, just {point the mouse|use your right thumbstick} to look and {press the WSAD or arrow keys|use your right thumbstick} to move. If you need to jump over something, press the {space bar|A button}. 
Good luck, visitor!</Text>
    </HelpItem>
    <HelpItem>
      <Entity>villageSign2</Entity>
<Text>Problem Plaza. This statue was erected for the villagers of Carbwir to honor the brave Koowaalaa who, years ago, brought great prosperity to the village. For each of the eight Development Goals of the United Nations he solved for our village, a symbol has been forged out of the purest gold. The more a goal is present in the village (i.e. more food), the more the symbol will shine. If the goal is poorly represented, the symbol will decay.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
    <HelpItem>
      <Entity>villageSign3</Entity>
      <Text>Warning, these stables are unstable! Do not attempt to have a picnic here, or you may become food for the vultures. Unless you are foolish enough to try and repair the sable, please go away.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
    <HelpItem>
      <Entity>villageSign4</Entity>
      <Text>Please, drink you own water, our well has been standing dry for so long, we don't even know if it will work if we ever get water in it again.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
    <HelpItem>
      <Entity>villageSign5</Entity>
      <Text>To all people of Carbwir: This gate has been locked. Not because we wanted to, but because it's rusted shut, and we don't have the key anymore. It got lost a while ago, when someone tried to polish the Plaza with it, and it fell. Don't go try to get it back though, it's stuck in the Plaza itself. So, let's just wait until the WVHO helps us replace the gates.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign01</Entity>
      <Text>Well hello, Tubbles! Yes, we know your name. No, it's not because we are weird living sign thingies, it's because Morwir painted this. Haha! Right. Let's go ahead and teach you a thing or two about the Dreamworld. As you can see, it's quite blank and abstract. This way, you won't lose any attention to nice frilly things which would distract you from the purpose of why you are here: to solve problems. Should you ever get into a situation here in the Dreamworld in which you see no way out, have no fear, we are here! Also, you can just press {escape|start} and return to the real world. If you wish to continue the tutorial, walk to the arrow.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign02</Entity>
      <Text>See those big purple blocks and smoke in front of you? Those are groups. Blocks with the same color are in the same group. They will come in all sorts of shapes and configurations, but for now, we will keep things easy. The blocks have a groupcenter, indicated by the smoke. The color of the smoke indicates which group it belongs to. You can't stand on group centers, but you can stand on blocks. Move on to the next arrow. </Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign03</Entity>
      <Text>Please look to your right. There are two groups over there, orange and green. Both have one block and a groupcenter. A small crosshair has appeared, to help you selecting groups. Just aim the crosshair at a block in the group you want to select and the group will be highlighted, indicating it is selected. Now look to your left. The pink group consists of one block and a groupcenter. However, you can't select it. This is because the groupcenter is too far away from you. You can only select groups that are within a radius. If the groupcenter is not within this radius, the crosshair will change color and you can't select the group. Please walk to the next arrow.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign04</Entity>
      <Text>We will now explain the axle-gizmo. At the bottom of the screen, three cogs have appeared. Each cog represents an axle (X, Y and Z). One cog is rotating in a certain direction. If you have selected a group and {left-click|press B}, the group will rotate around it's groupcenter over the selected axle in the selected direction. You will try this later on, first we will explain a little more about the gizmo. To swap axles or it's spinning rotation, use {Q and E or the scrollwheel|the shoulderkeys}. Practice a bit with it before you try to solve any puzzle. So, move to the blue group in front of you.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign05</Entity>
      <Text>Try to select and rotate the group in front of you using the axle-gizmo, and then move to the next arrow.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign06</Entity>
      <Text>Right, let's put all the things you've learned to practice! In front of you is a red group, containing four blocks. Right now, you are standing on a gray block. Gray blocks are static, they cannot be moved. To get to the arrow at the other side, you need to stand on the red block right in front of you (just walk on it), select the red group and rotate it over the correct axle. Notice how you will rotate along with the group if you stand on it.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign07</Entity>
      <Text>Well done! The next thing you need to master, is jumping. You can jump the distance of one standard block, plus a little bit. This means you can jump to the next arrow from here, but not to the third block. Practice jumping by hopping over the gray blocks towards the green group in the distance. In case you've forgotten how to jump: press the {space bar|A button}.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign08</Entity>
      <Text>Not every block is placed next to another block. Sometimes, you need to rotate it towards you, and then jump on it in order to progress. This is also the case with the green group in front of you. Try to reach the arrow, using the green platform.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign09</Entity>
      <Text>Untill now, you only needed to rotate blocks over the blue, horizontal axle. However, blocks can also be rotated over the red and green axle. This is needed at the next group. Two things are happening here. First, you need to rotate the block the red or green axle. Second, you need to reuse the block in order to get to the arrow. Reusing blocks is something you'll need to do often in the puzzles. After you use a block, don't forget it if you try to go further into the puzzle. You may need it again. Try to get to the arrow above now, using the black block twice.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign10</Entity>
      <Text>Great! You're almost there, just one more thing. The blue block at the other side is locked in at it's right and left side, but also at the other side of it's groupcenter. This means you will have to use at least two axles to rotate it next to you. This is another trick you will often need to do in the Dreamworld, especially when puzzles get tougher. Practice your skill for one last time, get to the arrow!</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>tutorialSign11</Entity>
      <Text>Awesome, you did it! With the basics of the mechanics mastered, you are now ready to face the puzzles representing the eight Development Goals. And just in time, the potion is beginning to wear out. Good luck! </Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>puzzleSign01</Entity>
      <Text>Welcome back, Tubbles. I see you have chosen to enter the Dreamworld from the Unstable Stable, so the problem for this puzzle is Hunger. As you know, the stable has collapsed and the villagers have no viable source of food. If you're able to solve this puzzle, it's real world effect will be a rebuild stable and a foodsupply for the villagers. Move to the closest meadow to read how you can solve this puzzle.</Text>
    </HelpItem>
	<HelpItem>
      <Entity>puzzleSign02</Entity>
      <Text>As told, this puzzle is about food. To illustrate this, there are two pairs of cows in this puzzle. These cows can be selected and rotated just like you would with groups. However, the cows have a little twist on the usual mechanic. As you may have noticed, they have no group center! This is because they are eachothers center. Select one cow and it's pairing cow will become its center. Select the other cow and the first cow will become its center. Your goal is to get both pair of cows from this meadow to the meadow on the other side. Oh, and by the way: the cows are connected to their pairs through an invisible rope. They cannot be moved further apart or closer to eachother as they are right now, and if one cow falls over the edge, it will take its pair with him and both will be respawned in the meadow. Good luck! </Text>
    </HelpItem>
  </Items>
</Help>